{"ocean":[{"level":"1","type":"ocean","question":"I am big and blue and fishies like to swim in me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Olen valmistatud veest."},{"text":"Paatidele meeldib minu peal purjetada."},{"text":"Vaalad elavad siin."}],"options":[{"label":"Park","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ookean","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pilv","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"2","type":"ocean","question":"I have a shell and I move very slowly on the sand. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"Kannan oma maja selili."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib s√º√ºa merevetikaid."},{"text":"Olen roomaja."}],"options":[{"label":"Lind","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Kilpkonn","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Koer","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"3","type":"ocean","question":"I am a big fish with pointy teeth. I like to swim very fast. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mu hambad on v√§ga teravad."},{"text":"Olen kalat√º√ºp."},{"text":"Inimesed kardavad mind vahel."}],"options":[{"label":"Haid","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Delfiin","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Vaal","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"4","type":"ocean","question":"I am pink and live in a shell. You can sometimes hear the ocean when you hold me to your ear. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Olen k√µva kaitsev v√§liskiht."},{"text":"Sa v√µid mind k√µrva panna."},{"text":"Ô∏è Leiad mind rannast."}],"options":[{"label":"Kalju","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Merekarp","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Kepp","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"5","type":"ocean","question":"I have eight arms and live in the ocean. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mul on palju relvi."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib end kividesse peita."},{"text":"Ma v√µin tinti pritsida."}],"options":[{"label":"Kaheksajalg","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Krabi","isCorrect":false},{"label":"T√§htkuju","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"6","type":"ocean","question":"I jump and play in the ocean. I am very smart. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Teen kl√µpsivaid h√§√§li."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib veest v√§lja h√ºpata."},{"text":"Olen imetaja t√º√ºp."}],"options":[{"label":"Kajakas","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Delfiin","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pingviin","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"7","type":"ocean","question":"I am small and walk sideways on the beach. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mul on k√º√ºnised."},{"text":"K√µnnin naljakalt."},{"text":"Elan mere √§√§res."}],"options":[{"label":"T√§htkuju","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Krabi","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Merehobune","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"8","type":"ocean","question":"I am very big and sing a song in the ocean. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Minu laulu saab kuulda kaugel."},{"text":"Olen suurim loom Maal."},{"text":"Ma puhun oma puhuaugust vett v√§lja."}],"options":[{"label":"Kala","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Vaal","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tihend","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"9","type":"ocean","question":"I am long and thin and can give you a zap! Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"Oskan s√§det teha"},{"text":"Ma n√§en v√§lja nagu madu"},{"text":"‚ñ´Ô∏è Hoia minust eemale"}],"options":[{"label":"Elektriangerjas","isCorrect":true},{"label":"S√§ga","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Seadragon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}},{"level":"10","type":"ocean","question":"I am shaped like a star and live on the ocean floor. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mul on viis k√§tt."},{"text":"Ma ei liigu v√§ga palju."},{"text":"‚≠ê Ma n√§en v√§lja nagu t√§ht."}],"options":[{"label":"Krabi","isCorrect":false},{"label":"T√§htkuju","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Meduusi","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"üåä"}}],"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Moo!' What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mulle meeldib rohtu s√º√ºa."},{"text":"Inimesed joovad mu piima."},{"text":"Mul on mustvalged laigud."}],"options":[{"label":"Koer","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lehm","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Kass","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I go quack, quack. I like to swim in a pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Olen beebina kollane."},{"text":"Mul on suur ja lame nokk."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib vesi."}],"options":[{"label":"Pardike","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Siga","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hobune","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I meow and like to chase string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mulle meeldib l√µngaga m√§ngida."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib kala s√º√ºa."},{"text":"Mul on pehmed k√§pad."}],"options":[{"label":"Koer","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Kass","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Linnuke","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I bark and wag my tail. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mulle meeldib luid n√§rida."},{"text":"Kaitsen teie maja."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib fetchi m√§ngida."}],"options":[{"label":"Linnuke","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Koer","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Kala","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mulle meeldib s√º√ºa maap√§hkleid."},{"text":"Olen v√§ga suur."},{"text":"Kasutan oma pagasiruumi vee pritsimiseks."}],"options":[{"label":"Elevant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ahv","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Karu","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I like to hop and have long ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mulle meeldib porgandeid s√º√ºa."},{"text":"Mul on kohev saba."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib rohus m√§ngida."}],"options":[{"label":"Orav","isCorrect":false},{"label":"J√§nes","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Kilpkond","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I swing from trees and eat bananas. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mulle meeldib s√µpradega m√§ngida."},{"text":"Elan d≈æunglis."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib ronida."}],"options":[{"label":"L√µvi","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ahv","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tiiger","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I am the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mul on suur lakk."},{"text":"Olen oran≈æ ja pruun."},{"text":"Mul on teravad k√º√ºnised."}],"options":[{"label":"L√µvi","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Karu","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hunt","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I hiss and slither on the ground. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Mul ei ole jalgu."},{"text":"Mulle meeldib end rohu sisse peita."},{"text":"Mul on kahvliga keel."}],"options":[{"label":"Uss","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Madu","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sisalik","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I swim in the ocean and have sharp teeth. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"Olen kalat√º√ºp."},{"text":"Elan meres."},{"text":"M√µned arvavad, et olen hirmus"}],"options":[{"label":"Delfiin","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Haid","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Vaal","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"üêæ"}}]}